Ryder Antiques offers Swedish and French original painted country furniture and folk art. We emphasize the Empire Periods and earlier.

Menu

Recent Posts

* [English Passenger and Mail Coach. (click for summary).](https://www.ryderantiques.com/ryder-antiques-main/english-passenger-and-mail-coach/) June 1, 2024

[Home](https://www.ryderantiques.com/) / Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

Who we are
----------

Our website address is: https://www.ryderantiques.com and we are in Burlington, Ontario, Canada.

What personal data we collect and why we collect it
---------------------------------------------------

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://www.ryderantiques.comx5x.732.myftpupload.com//ln9.47f.myftpupload.comautomattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Contact forms

Your information is used to contact you and potentially stored for the length of time that it takes to respond to your contact request.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have crated an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for one year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

### Who we share your data with

Google analytics is used to provide us with metrics to help us to improve our website, sales, and the customer experience.

### How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

What rights you have over your data
-----------------------------------

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

Where we send your data
-----------------------

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

Your contact information
------------------------

Currently your contact information exists in our newsletter database if you have subscribed to our newsletter. It is also possible that if you have bought from us in the past and are not part of the newsletter then your contact information may be stored elsewhere, offline currently. Your data may be added to our customer database, which is not shared or public.

Additional information
----------------------

Nothing currently.

Search for:  Search 

Antique categories Select a category Pottery and Porcelain Sold Items Antique Boxes Antique Church Items and Antique Carvings Antique Lighting Swedish and French Antique Tall case, Wall and Table Clocks Antique Decorative Pieces Notable Pieces Antique Folk Art Antique Painted Furniture Antique Hooked Rugs Antique Mirrors Antique Painting Recent Additions SALE Antique Textiles

Collection Cloud

Our Newsletter

First Name 

Email address: 

Leave this field empty if you're human: 

Posts

* [English Passenger and Mail Coach. (click for summary).](https://www.ryderantiques.com/ryder-antiques-main/english-passenger-and-mail-coach/) June 1, 2024
* [Antique decorative boxes](https://www.ryderantiques.com/ryder-antiques-main/antique-decorative-boxes/) December 2, 2020
* [Some light at the end of the tunnel for the antiques industry.](https://www.ryderantiques.com/ryder-antiques-main/some-light-at-the-end-of-the-tunnel-for-the-antiques-industry/) June 1, 2020
* [Circa 1450 Florence silk and velvet textile.](https://www.ryderantiques.com/ryder-antiques-main/circa-1450-florence-silk-and-velvet-textile/) March 26, 2018
* [Napoleonic Porcelain Urn.](https://www.ryderantiques.com/ryder-antiques-main/napoleonic-porcelain-urn/) February 23, 2018

Popular Tags

Contact Us

Your Name (required)  

Your Email (required)  

Your Phone (required)  

Your Message  

Δ

All rights reserved © Ryder Antiques 2001 - 2020  

* Search
    
    Search for:  Search
